http://www.psls.org/privacypolicy

Home
Store
About Us
Who Is PSLS?
Consumers
Why Do I Need A Surveyor?
How to Access PSLS Member Information
What Kind of Information Is in Members Section?
Website Privacy Policy
I. PurposeBecause PSLS wants to build user trust and confidence in the web site and demonstrate a commitment to privacy and online data security, we are disclosing our privacy practices to you.II. Use of InformationWhen you visit our site, your privacy is important to us, so we do not release your personal information to third parties without your consent.III. Third-Party AccessThe Web site contains links to other sites. Pennsylvania Society of Land Surveyors is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of those Web sites. Third parties may collect information about you when you click on advertising or content on their Web sites; we do not control the collection of such information. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party Web sites you access.IV. Security MeasuresTo safeguard your personal information when you use our online forms, we protect it with a secure socket layer (SSL) encryption.  If you choose to send us an e-mail instead of using our secure online form, you should be aware that e-mail is not necessarily safe from interception. If your communication includes sensitive information, such as a credit card number, and you do not wish to use our online form, please contact us via phone, fax, or mail.V. Use of CookiesOur website does not make use of cookies.VI. Contact UsIf you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:E-mail: psls@psls.org | Phone: 717-441-6057 | Fax: 717-236-2046908 N. Second St. | Harrisburg, PA 17102
Updated January 27, 2020
P: 717.441.6057 | F: 717.236.2046 | psls@psls.org
908 N 2nd Street | Harrisburg, PA 17102
Privacy Policy * Site Map
Donate to PSLS Programs
Donate to PSLS PAC
© 2020 Pennsylvania Society of Land Surveyors
Powered by Wild Apricot Membership Software
